you taught me what power was showing me everything you were willing to betray for it
your heat still poisons the air that i breathe i don't put daggers in my cool your master
i own but co2 is the only truth we've got be all be all sisters heard astonishing tales of
impossible it's just you and me again but it's kind of funny though beware of like you know
It's pretty sickening. I no wonder people go crazy in this world, right?
It's like how people treat each other, especially...
But anyway, you know, I have one person, but I don't know if I have just myself, you know,
but it was kind of like, you know, I did do this show to like connect with people, right?
What's the point of the rules, you know? Do they break them or they won't be here to follow them?
I don't know, I don't know what's wrong with people.
Very few people you can trust, right?
So there's Tux, Tuxi, Tuxi, Tuxito.
He's having a little dinner
that he just came in tonight.
Tuxi, my babe, he's very beautiful.
He and Lola are really getting along, they're really cute.
And, oh, look at that, it's better to love and lost
and never have loved at all.
I don't know about that.
I don't know, it's kind of cliche a little bit.
Little bit cliche, but uh, I mean I can't help but love but it's like I mean jeez
It's like even though even though it's like you you know you love, uh, I don't know
Pour your love pour your love into somebody
Watch them just pour it out. That's kind of worse than and moving in the first place rather
Like you don't know what you lose. What's what's another cliche? I could say yes, that's it
Anyway
It's really funny.
I did get a nice compliment from that, you know,
careless Kate, I think it was a compliment.
She said, oh yeah, well, he's a, you know,
he's a creative owner of his body.
So, but, oh, but he, and he relies on this overpriced AI.
Well, that's the compliment
because I don't pay for it.
So, about that.
So you think it's so good that it costs something?
It's free.
Actually, how about creative? I don't know, you know, she is actually really creative because, you know, what she did with her picture
I mean, she turned herself into Darcy Silva
If you know Nani De Fiance, I mean if you've seen Kate, you know, she looks like an ogre, but, or ogre, I'm sorry, but
Yeah, her AI photo of herself, how much it's that of cost in order to transform her into
Should I say Catwoman?
I don't know.
Yeah.
That's like, is that the photo you're
going to bring into your plastic surgeon, though?
I'm just wondering.
It's like, you know, you used a blue song.
You can play a harmonic on.
Oh, sure.
I mean, it's like, yeah, there's so much you
can do with it.
I mean, it's like, you know, the thing is with it
is it's, you know, work with it.
Don't rely on it, but don't.
I mean, it's like, if you have a talent,
Magnify it, right?
If you don't then you just you just don't but it's like I
Just I just don't have I don't know and then it's like what you say something about like oh, I just make a bunch of diss songs
I think I know I made her hey baby. I know I made you know Christine got run over by a ranger
I think that might have been my best song like this song but that was Christmas and I wrote that song
Oh, hi, babe, and I wrote Vita's biscuits, too.
Hold on, let's see.
Oh, there he goes.
Oh, you saw him.
There he goes, just ran into my bedroom.
But yeah, you can play along with it,
sing along with it, you know.
Fortunately, I mean, I'm not a good singer.
I don't know about a little bit of a lower voice
of a baritone, but I don't know.
Just like the one thing I regret is like, you know,
having this woman, you know, you know,
this monster, which she basically is, you know.
Being so nicer and then and how quickly things do things turn, right?
I would have loved like, you know
You know just the courtesy of like talk to me one-on-one
About something if the people have a problem
But no, they want to do everything like right out in the open in front of everybody, right and then
Yeah, and then work out nothing
It's just really ridiculous.
Let me put on, not like anyone wants to come up,
but let's see if anyone wants to come up, we'll see.
By the way, is my hairline really that bad?
I don't know.
Just pull all the way back, you can see my hairline.
I think I've had the same hairline since I was like 15.
I had these little places where my horn used to be,
my horn's horn.
But hold on a second, we'll see what happens.
Well, I do have one thing to look forward to at least maybe J-Dog and I will get to have a dance at the gay club
I don't know if that will happen. You know a lot of plans fall through
Okay, so both that video the last one was about
You know that's part four of the ten part series. I'm releasing
Telling the entire story of Cupid and Psyche, which I did tell like acapella or what is it without music or you know
From from the heart when they started you remember you would recommend a really fancy haircut
I don't even know what that would look like. I mean, it's like I remember like on last Mother's Day
I got a Ryan Gosling
From the Barbie movie or something like that without the bleached bleached hair. I mean, yeah
I mean, it's like I do have a lot. I do a really long hair
I mean, I don't wear, I don't even have gray in my hair.
People like, they don't even believe like,
I don't dye my hair.
I mean, look how massive my hair is.
I mean, it's like, you know, it is crazy.
It could be like cousin it, you know, here there are there and now I look now now that it's preferred
You know, I'm sure that would prefer
And they I was like joking with you know when beat it was on and I put my hair up and in pony tails
They acted like I was serious like that was like in my style, but I'll try that but she's like oh
She's making fun of my braids or something. I wasn't braiding yet. I mean that'd be really cool if I could braid
I just don't know how I don't know how girls could do that. I mean, it's like they were like, you know
They could always just braid
Anything. I can't even twist it up, but I can put it up in
Pippi Longstockings
You could upload a picture and try out different haircuts. I could I could do that
Yeah, let me just I mean I can just try it like this. I can just do different styles
See how this looks. Okay, so I got that what they got that part. Yeah, okay
You can do it like this
Just try out different stuff. My mom was a hairdresser. She doesn't she didn't do it
I mean she has her beauty license and she still renews it. I think but you know that she never practiced in a salon
But my actually my sister-in-law
Her father came from Italy, right?
his name was Flavio and
He had a beauty school. I might actually show that someday
Hi, Katie, how are you?
She had a hair cutting school, right, and she was featured on this show called Tabitha
Takes Over or something like that, and this is an Australian woman named Tabitha.
Where's my other brand?
I lost it.
Yeah, there's a woman named Tabitha.
And she comes in and she like fixes us along.
And there's a, what was the guy's name?
I don't know, it was really, yeah, it was interesting.
I have it somewhere on my, like saved, you know?
Okay, let me just fix it.
I'm just gonna give myself a long ponytail.
It looks kind of dumb with just one side of it.
Oh, but yeah, I mean, it's like,
I mean, I know I have pretty good hair.
You're good, you're just tired.
Yeah, I'm kind of tired too.
You know, I was talking to somebody
and then they were just like,
You know, I guess I said something they didn't like or something or, you know, this is a person I like, you know
Talked to for a long time and listen. I said one thing. They're like, oh, I can't talk to you anymore
And then there's this hung up on me
Kind of like that's like one of the worst things is like being silence, you know, I don't like that
Just say you can say
You can say oh, can we change the topic or something that it's just like oh
it was just like the way it was done I don't know kind of like I just said I
don't know I'm kind of surprised how I'm treated sometimes not like a mean
person but it's like I need to push more and more
ripping off my Jeffrey Dalmer glasses there we go how's that for how's that for a
look there we go so yeah I do like these glasses
Teemo $5. Yeah, I mean, it's like I'm not I'm not cheap. I'm a Capricorn. I'm just thrifty
Thank you so much. Oh, yeah. Well, there we go. I do you have hey look at this, too
What's the weather like I wonder where's anybody from you like the Dahmer Dahmer take two. Yeah, there we go
I mean, all I need is like a fucking
Car and I you know set of knives. Okay, but yeah, like what's so what's the weather and we're shout out where you're from?
Let me see
It was in California, you like it?
I like kind of cute, huh?
Let me see, I'll say San Jose.
You can even say the weather anywhere.
You can say like, you know, Prague or whatever.
Like a weather San Jose.
Let's see if this works.
Do you know the way to San Jose?
Ba, ba, ba, ba, ba.
Okay.
Oh, 71 degrees.
Yeah, I mean that, I was pretty impressed with myself.
I was actually very, I was able to
program the weather into night. It's not easy. It involves, you know, putting name
server, different name servers on your website and and working with a lot of
code. Oh, I love Palm Springs. Actually, I, you know, I had vacationed a lot in
Palm Springs. You know, we have a property there. But since that was
little, yeah, that was like my favorite thing. Palm Springs used to be this great
destination for
Celebrities back in like the 50s 60s and that's where all the celebrities would go hide out because it's two hours from Los Angeles
Just go on the on the freeway
And you pass these these like big dinosaurs. It's actually they're featured in Peewee's big adventure and
And then you drive into Palm Springs. It's like this little oasis in the middle of this desert and it's a little perfect little
beautiful place and there's
Also Palm Desert, which has some golf courses and stuff. I don't like the golf but my you know my family does but
I just like to be in the pool, the jacuzzi.
It can be like over a hundred degrees there.
Oh, look at there.
It's 87 in Palm Springs.
11 at, sorry, oh my God, 11 at night.
Hi, gorgeous, Ms. Liz.
See, look, Ms. Liz thinks I look good, you know.
I could kind of like kind of my confidence is kind of like decreasing since I'm often constantly compared to Cyrus Iraq's
But you know, I know in my heart. I don't look like him
You know, I mean I have a few less scabs on my scalp
I have a few more teeth and I'm a little bit a few more brain cells. I'm not you know
I'm not gonna fall for some guy on a voice changer having phone sex with me, but
People shouldn't be playing with the mentally disabled like that. I mean almost like
I feel sorry for him if he wasn't such a bastard.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, it's really sad.
But, you know, there's an interesting quote I saw
on this website called Kiwi Farms.
And it's like, there's a little, thank you so much.
There's very little difference between watching Cyrax
and being Cyrax, right?
And so these people that are basically, that's the thing.
So it's like, you know, and I would say, you know,
there's very little difference between like, you know,
You know calling somebody a low cow and watching low cows and interacting with them and actually being one yourself
I mean, it's like it's kind of hard. You kind of like people become what they hate. I guess and so
Try not to hate but yeah, yeah, but it's interesting. Yeah, I guess
Well, here's my other thing. Yeah
And you know what? But I did here's what I did like about that site because I was like, oh that site maybe is like, you know
Little
Sometimes I don't like the idea. You're busy. Okay. Thank you so much. I love you too. Thank you so much for dropping
I like I do need them right now because people are coming and dropping dislikes and stuff, but
Yeah, but I forgot where I was going with that, but look here. I have this little little fairy in here
Look at the view scene. This one
Really cool. It's like a little
little jar
It's a little fairy like hot in the woods
And it's pretty cool
limited edition number 27. The only one of them. Dr. Worthington is a Greg Ged Anon from
Edinburgh, Scotland. Mummified. It's a mummified fairy. Yeah. Oh, Paul Springs, The Salton Sea.
The Salton Sea is a great movie. That is about Kilmer, I believe, and it's about meth. It's about meth.
But okay, so Palm Springs does have this big gay scene
So what we used to go in as a kid and they had this spring break in Palm Springs
And we'd go when we were a kid and there'd be like women and like thong bikinis on the backs of motorcycles
And then and so it was a real big party place and like for the spring break
But then like the city kind of started cracking down on it. And so then it turned into the gay
like area, or actually like senior citizens than gays.
And so there's basically a lot of old gay people
that I'm just gonna, no, no.
But they have these things called the white party there.
And yeah, when I was a teenager, I used to go
and when all the gay people would be there
at certain time of the year and boy, was that popular.
But I could never even go out.
I mean, even when I was in my twenties,
I was like, you know, kind of still treated like a kid.
But.
Yeah, it's never really I've never really felt like I grew up in some ways because I was always like just like treated like a kid in some ways
You know, I still am
Because I am like on the younger side of you know the brothers and sisters or it's like you know
The older brothers and sisters of the younger brothers and sisters
Right now. I'm in the middle of all those but I'm the only one you know not married and look at this
Okay, we go all lurkers must present themselves before the High Council of bad decisions. I love it. I love it. Yeah
It is a bad decision to lurk here because, you know, I'm magical, you know what I do
to lurkers?
I make them eventually talk, eventually they'll rebuild themselves, but I'm not making it
this way.
You can go, okay, you can go un-lurk and then you can like reveal yourself, you just type
un-lurk.
And then, I mean, you're here.
But yeah, I think a lot of people just like to watch.
They must be like a bunch of cucks, because, you know, a cuck is somebody that just likes
to watch.
Um, but you know, I'm not insulting if you're just a natural person that that likes to watch I understand
That's fine. You don't participate in the chat
But if you're one of these new people that are just a hate watching it's like how about go look in the mirror
What's that song go hate yourself? Ah?
Go hate yourself. Oh
Yeah, that's the um, they psyche is a haters club song. It's like what's that song from I actually wrote that song
I'm actually, I impress myself sometimes.
Okay, did I go through two books of matches already?
Gosh darn it, and I should have gotten another,
oh my God, yeah, okay.
I've been through two books of matches already.
Not good.
Okay, but I'm gonna go lay this on the stove.
And I'm gonna get something to eat, hold on.
Bear back.
People sometimes say like I don't like biscuits,
like look what I got.
I like biscuits.
Look at this biscuit roll-ups. I like them here. Let me get my little my little staff
Where does down session? This is my weapon. Oh, so, you know my neighbor that hates me. I ran into him today
Like he was walking and I knew that would just be a matter of time, but I was walking out. Hey 2020
How are you good to see you? I was walking out walking back home from the store and
my neighbor
Was walking out with this dog and his girlfriend his girlfriend immediately started crossing the street
And so she was going to their side this year. She had one of the dogs and I love dogs, right?
How could they hate me?
Because I was like, you know Bita came on the other night and started screaming at me
I said my mom was, you know, ugly and all kinds of horrible things.
And so I started to get kind of yelling back and I guess like he was walking by my house.
The door was open.
He started kicking my door and then I went down and I was like, you don't have to kick
my door.
You know, just like, you know, yell up, please be quiet or just, you know, knock or something.
And then I closed the door.
Then he ripped off my ring doorbell through it through the window broke the window in there
It's been fixed, but then the windows already fucked up again because that's not fucked up
But it's like it
They just took the frame and put a new window in it
But when I opened it the frame is coming off of it already
So I don't mind you to have them come back and fix that of course. It's just my life, right?
It's like of course. Yeah, but um, yeah, they do hate me
because they think that I am responsible for like the
the cement being delivered and they think, you know,
oh, what are you doing?
All you do is get McDonald's and come back and blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, he's like a short guy.
He's like probably like five foot two or something like that.
And, but yeah, so basically I just walked by them.
And it's like, you know what?
If, like, I'm a bad person, their dogs would have started barking at me or something like that.
Dogs, like, like, like me, like, because animals like me.
It's like, I don't know where this thing is, like, and my animals hate me.
Or is that, oh my gosh, look at Lenore right now.
This is Lenore. Look at Lenore.
She's up on the speaker, like, sleeping.
Is that cozy, Lenore?
What are you doing? I see you up there.
Oh, you're yawning? You had to yawn?
Okay.
Is there Rudy back in the corner over there?
I know Rudy likes to be in the corner over there.
No, I don't cuz I fit him in the corner. He just like sit on the table over there. Hi Rudy. I see you over there
And is Lola on the couch? Oh, there's miss Lola. Hi. I see you too. Oh, I see you
You're just that's where that's your spot. Yeah
Yeah, I mean I'm like I used to I had a neighbor and when I lived in San Pedro, California, right?
I lived there for a short time a few years and I had a neighbor and he was just he was really cute
And he was a waiter and he had a girlfriend and stuff and but he would come up and we would smoke weed and like
you know there I started having problems and
Because other people of course this number it wasn't like it's like it's like it really not wasn't me actually
And so when I was in Glendale, I had almost all my windows broken out
Like people would just say break them because I would like not let them in the house and stuff like that and
It was kind of like a little bit trappy trappy
You know, I'll be right back. I need to light this again. I'll tell you a story
So there is this guy the guy that eventually ended up stabbing me and stuff the guy that stabbed me in the ear
and I actually ended up killing my neighbor a year later and then he hung himself in jail.
Yeah, so one time, like, I wouldn't let him in the house or whatever, and he came back,
was banging on the door and I was like, get the fuck away, go away, go away. And he had with him a rope.
And a fire extinguisher later. I found his plan was to knock me out with a fire extinguisher and then tie me up
And put me in the closet or something like that or something. I don't know
I mean, he was gonna tie me up for me somewhere
But I wouldn't let him in and so then he kicked out my window
But then he like he heard his leg like really bad. He's sort of bleeding
I mean, it's so then he with Taco Bell in the ambulance. It was a whole thing. Yeah, I had a very interesting time
I mean, I do have some interesting stories
you know
But yeah, he ended up stabbing me.
That was probably like the third or fourth time
he tried to kill me, but the first few times
I was able to like look him in the eye
and like stare him down and made him stop.
And one of the times when he chased me out with a knife,
I gave him a cigarette and then he changed.
He went because he was crazy, so he changed.
He went back to normal when he gave him a cigarette.
But yeah, so I was able to do that.
But then like the time when he like knocked out all the lights in my house
And then was like fighting with his girlfriend and about to probably kill her and I got in the middle of them trying to defend her
that's when he stabbed me in the ear and
I thought I was gonna die actually, I bled a lot.
There was blood all over the floor.
It was like, I thought he just punched me in the ear
until I felt it like fill up with blood.
And then I was bleeding.
And I was like, and then he came back the next day.
And that's when he got arrested and stuff
because the neighbor called the cops and stuff.
But yeah, interesting times.
But yeah, I know, yeah.
I mean, it's like, so that's why I kind of like,
Kind of keep myself away from people because it's like I tend to attract
volatile personalities crazy people. I don't I don't know but um, I
Don't know and I'm very I'm very nice person
But it's like I was too nice at that point where and it's like, you know always like wanting
some kind of acceptance that I can never get right and
then
But even on this show like you know, I was I guess I was popular last year or whatever, but
That I wasn't really it was just to kind of was like I look back. I was like really nice and I was like really like
You know, I just let people do what they wanted to do basically, but you know
Sometimes I couldn't take it and I was like I was not even on the panel a lot of time
I would just leave and I was supposed to be like I know like on like, you know
In charge of the show and stuff
avoid because you know even the people I'm attracted to are usually like
criminals unfortunately but I don't like you know I like I'm like dorky
enough I don't need another I don't need some dork I need I like you know I like
bad boy kind of energy but I figured out like I probably should find like some
kind of rehabilitated Christian
Like a guy that like found God in jail or something and then like comes out and he's like rehabilitated
I think I need that kind of guy, but he still has the tattoos and he still has like the attitude a little bit and can like
You know stick up for me, but I
Don't know
Then once I get too much in the Jesus, they don't like gay people sometimes, you know, so it's all I had to be it's hard
The right person will feel right. Yeah, I'm kind of but I haven't given up on uh on that, right?
I don't, I don't believe in love, no I do, I do believe in love but if it's meant to
happen it will happen but you know I'm not really looking for it and then it's
like I'm not really out there to find it either. I'd have to have some kind of like
Disney
Um got you know night on a white horse just find me or something like that. Oh
Look at their turn blow. I know love. It's a beautiful thing if you want to come up. I can love on you a little bit
I know I'm not really
Here's my link if you want to come up and chat. I don't know
It's like I'm having a hard time lately and just like you know, and I'm sure people some people will be like
Yeah
Think oh bang. Oh, yeah, I don't know. It's like a
You know, I must I must suffer for love or like I'm a romantic
I'm a very romantic person like so it's like that's why I'm not really into like I'm not even into sex really
I think it's like whenever it's always would sound good and then when I would actually do it
It would be really boring and I'd be like this is boring. Can we like get get to like something?
Can we watch TV or something? I just want to hang out and like, you know cuddle or something like that
I don't need to like have actual sex. I mean, it's like it's a little bit extreme for me
so
Or else I can get it. You're very sensitive. Yeah, I mean it's a blessing and a curse. I'm an empath. I'm also like I'm very like
Even if you look into something called human design, it's like it's kind of incorporates Kabbalah astrology
And the chakras and it's like we have this chart and it has in my head. I
Love cuddle. Yeah, that's what I wanted you. I just want to hug somebody sometimes, right? But um, yeah
I have like I know I have a wide open
like
Crown and a wide open third eye. Like they're just wide open. It's like and so
Everything I'm just like so receptive. That's why I'm a good psychic and I'm look some people don't believe I am I am
I'm very good psychic and I do I
have I have
See the voices in my head are not usually not my voices and that's why it gets kind of hard
It's not schizophrenia because it's like they're real voices. They're like they're like
some of them are the dead, some of them are God, some of them are spirits, almost
all the same thing. You're the opposite. Yeah, you might be here. So it's like,
that's kind of like, see, I have a I have a feminine kind of mind. I have a very
feminine brain because females in a receptive because of vagina. Chaos, yeah.
Oh, there was chaos today. Yeah, there's been a lot of chaos lives. It's like,
You know, a lot of people are mad at me and like it's like, you know, I hate me now
Really not for a great reason because they hate somebody else and then
That I don't have a problem with I guess I mean it's like but I don't even think that person likes me very much
And so it's not even like, you know, is it worth it all in the end? It's like
I do have spirits telling me things like to go in a certain direction. Thank you. Thank you
Being human is a real thing. Yeah, but so is being a spirit like
Like we're both
Like the the human is like the car. It's like the shell. It's uh, it's nothing without the spirit
That's why it's like and not animated without the spirit
Movie night. Yeah, we got to do that soon. Let's do that soon. I think you need to lay in the cigar
Thank you Liz I know and you've always been nice and you know
Like the people that are here and talking and stuff. It's like they get it
They're usually unless it's like, you know, Lady Bathory or or, you know, Bita or something like that
And they're just gonna, you know, say I'm a piece of human garbage or whatever, but
There's a lot of people that do love me I appreciate
Yeah, it's been like, you know, it's probably been six weeks and it's like
You know, I'm still and I still haven't really changed my mind about things
I don't like how I've been necessarily treated by even the people I tried to help in the situation
who are kind of like I feel a little bit like right right right me off a little bit or
Think I'm like stupid or something. Hey Patrick. Good to see you. Good to see you
Because it's like, you know, I did kind of like
Bad mods. Yeah, I mean, I have good like, you know, Jamie's a great mod. I really like, you know
Throughout the time I've modded a lot of people and like but nobody really wanted a mod. It's like and so it's like and it's like
They banned you. Oh
Did someone ban 2020? I don't
They put the time you out. I'm sorry
Yeah, I mean, it's like that's why I mean it. That's why sometimes
Jamie did Jamie you didn't do it. I don't think she did
I've learned a lot from
Let me see if you're a band or something. Hold on. Where's my tablet? I
Don't know she she said she did it so she did it
Yeah, I mean it's like I mean I bet there okay, so here's like the thing with modding
for me
It's like I can do I can do it and it's like I unbanned most people because that's like now
I've gotten to the point really don't care. I'll look who did it. Hold on. Let me see. I
Don't really you know, I don't
It's like, you know, they're just gonna come on alts and stuff like that. I can't really prevent
Who comes in here?
It's like a losing thing like, you know, because it's like, you know, if they're determined, you know
If I'm determined to go somewhere. I mean, I have a bunch of accounts too
I have, you know, I do have several accounts.
Just throughout the years,
I've developed a lot of Gmail accounts.
Okay, so let me go to my thing.
I'll see what happened.
Because maybe it was just Nightbot or something.
I don't know.
It can be like, you know, who knows.
Let me see.
But I doubt that Jamie did it.
Oh, I don't doubt.
I know she didn't.
I don't know she didn't.
Because she doesn't do that.
Okay, so we'll see what happened though.
Let's get to my.
Page, okay
Okay
Let me see what I see in the chat. Let me see this anyone timed out
I don't see a hold on. Well, I don't know it. I don't see anything. Oh
Okay, well come on he came in peace. Okay. Yeah, I didn't I didn't see him
Say, I mean, it's like Alexander McQueen we tend to we tend to time people out
So yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't know if sometimes people are just like
Yeah
Well, I don't know you have to work that out with her. Maybe I don't know
Maybe I don't know if you ever had a problem with anybody. I don't know
It's like there is like, you know, this kind of be the beef
I know going on with some people and I don't know there gets there
But I'm I apologize. I mean, I don't I think it couldn't have been more than 30 seconds
But it's always good. It is good to maybe talk about it with them. Yeah
Yeah, I think it was just 30 seconds
Yeah
Um, I yeah, but it's like yeah, because it's like then that then people because people take it personally
I think it personally if I was timed out or and stuff like that sometimes because I never know sometimes if it's for 24 hours
Or whatever and so it's always better to like talk things out if you have a conflict
You know, and I'm sorry if I haven't been facilitating people getting along because maybe there's like, you know unsaid things or or that kind of thing and so
Okay
Yeah, um, because you know, that's like kind of an Alex McQueen move and it's like and then that caused a big
Problem when he started doing it then I started getting threatened to get swatted and stuff
I other people not not being really 20-20, but it's like by other people and it's like and I was kind of letting Alexander
Yeah, but if you go ahead and if you have like you should talk things out because I at least like you know
Or if you have them or if you do a problem with somebody you can always them hide them or whatever
But I don't I don't know, you know, I don't I'm sorry 20 20, you know
If I have to I'll start modding people again
I don't want people modding with their feelings because that's a bronze bird move because bronze bird likes to mod with his
Pee-Pee's like he's coming out for 24 hours wherever I am and it's like and then nobody wants like I'm not really a mod anywhere
I've been unmodded pretty much by everybody and so it's not safe for me
So I think I'm just gonna start going to
You know not going to other rooms. I don't know. I don't want to be so depressed tonight. It's just like
Basically, I mean I am getting to the point where there's like so few people here and talking that it's like I don't really want people to be
to be banned
because
You know, I like people participating even if like, you know, you just agree with them
But I'm not gonna get mad at people or like, you know, but just like, you know
Even but yeah, it's like just warnings are good or it's like or talk about your problems and stuff
I'm not I don't get mad at people
But you know, I'm having a like a you know a weird time right now. I don't need more enemies
I know I know I know he's not banned. I know it was just a timeout
It was like but some people don't know like if it's 24 hours if it's 10 seconds if it's and like why sometimes
Yeah
So I guess it was just for a few seconds
Yeah, your band earlier, I know well as it was just a timeout it was in a band band is like hidden
It's like the
It's like the the abyss is that Emma Levi-Tin used to call it. Okay. We have a guest coming on. Oh look
Hold on
What's up?
This is a treat
How are you doing today? I think I came to surprise you today use this surprise me look at
You're you have no sure I love it. I'm trying to make sure you fall in love again
Wow
I'm speechless. Hi. How are you?
300 we have 300 glow here
Sex oh my god, you got some alcohol tonight. I wish I had some alcohol. Yeah, I'm not drinking. I got my alcohol
Okay
Yeah, well, you know, um J dog asked me out on a Saturday night. Oh, you go dancing at a gay club J dog
you know J dog is
He's like a dog is trying to steal you from me. I know isn't that crazy?
Yeah, I made a move. I know he's making moves. I don't know. I mean, it's like that out of J though
I think he's funny
Yeah, I like J-Dog. He's like, hey, let's go to a gay bar and he's like, I'll dance with you and stuff like that
I don't know if I don't think it will get beyond that but I might like you know dancing is crazy
But we can hang out. Okay. Yeah, I mean, I'm not much of a dancer and stuff. Yeah, we can I mean, yeah
I'm like respectful to what you're gonna do the
I'm going to do the bat to see it's called a bat to see a batman does it in the 1960s in the batman show
Yeah, it's snorkel
Yeah
Hey, guess who like that like sig came back like uh, he was in the chat like a little bit like a guest today
And then I he he posted a really strange picture of himself in the discord. I think this is him
Can you identify if this is a sig? I'll show you this picture that he posted. Yeah, show me that picture of signal
I said Santa? I mean, I don't know who he is, but I was like, I think this is, I think
this is Sig. So here's the picture that Sig posts. Let me see where it was. Okay.
He posted it. He looks actually he looks pretty good in it. It's one of those better pictures that he take
I think it probably looks like his like a let me see
The judge of that. This is a good picture of them guys. How does they look here? Oh?
Shit, what the fuck why he looked like that?
That's what he looks like. That's normal
Is that him that's a great he posted that on the discord. Yeah
He's in your discord?
Yeah, his name is Fuzzy the Bear or something like that.
No, that's Fuzzy Bear. Fuzzy Bear is a different guy.
Okay, that's Fuzzy Bear.
Okay, maybe Fuzzy Bear was just using a six picture or something like that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Shout out to Fuzzy Bear.
Okay, I'll make 2020 a standard moderator and I'll make you want to
300 but um, so you won't but you can still I guess you can still get timed out by the other month
But at least you'll have I could be a mob, but you know, I'm here in there
Mod is just like it's just kind of like a courtesy just to like, you know to show that you're like, you know friends and stuff
I'm really out here
Yo, thank you. So I think someone is trying to scan me. Okay. Tell me the story. What's going on?
So I got a call
That someone's trying to like
Extort me for some money. Okay. So the robot name was Suzanne the bot that called left the voicemail
Suzanne said
This is what Suzanne said. Hey, we're looking for 300 glow. Is this 300 glow?
If this is 300 if this is 300 glow
We're here to collect
We're here to serve papers and collect a debt or something like that. You say you say no, this is 400 blow
Yeah, and then I was like what the fuck?
Nobody calls you when it tells you paying me right now
Well, sir, right? I would think that you know, they're not very like slick these debt collectors nowadays
They have to I guess they have to identify them like you would think I would get a
Email, you know, you would get an email of your money to something
Or if it's not even in your email is through the mail you will get that
Well, yeah, so you know what the thing is it's like even if you're a credit card debt
But the credit card companies do is eventually they sell that debt to like a debt collection agency
For like pennies on the dollar and then the debt collection. So it basically
They you know, basically, you know all your like every seven years your credit clears up and it gets it's perfect again, right?
It's because they go off the thing and so but I'm trying not to like take too much credit right now
But I can use them
But yeah, just you know, sometimes I don't answer my phone. They always seem to track track people down
You know, it's just like, you know, just don't pick up the phone
Let's you know the number, but uh, yeah, I get all kinds of
But right, right, but why why would they call and try to like harass me like that? That's like harassment almost
Well, yeah, because it's like, they want to be paid, but you know, it's like, they basically
there's insurance that covers like people that don't pay, and so I don't know, our society's
great.
Even like the, like the grocery stores, if you people at shoplift, they put a premium
on everybody else that paying for groceries for the people at shoplift, and so it's all
paid for through insurance.
People shoplifting stuff. Right, right, but it's like, you know, so how do you think I should go about this wait for them?
Really send me something through the mail, right or email like you can't just call me a hey, I'm calling you pay me
Yeah, you're crazy. I mean, it's like, you know, even if they send stuff to your house
Or I mean, it's like they have to send like a court paper basically in the kitchen a court or something like that for anything that ever
yeah and uh so i don't know these debt collectors i know they're usually not very
You know, they're these well now they just do have the AI calling and doing it
So you said it was a robot calling or is a red for sure robot sounds like AI. They don't even care anymore. I mean, it's like
This stupid robot the stupid AI they said they're acting like I own them like three million dollars
They're like we're gonna show up to where you live
Like Jesus Christ, you have three million dollars. How would you go that much? That's crazy. Yeah, I don't know you tell me psyche. I
Don't know. I don't know. I mean, it's like, you know, I assume like me, you know, you're okay
You're in a house, right? You're in Los Angeles. Actually, you don't the real estate out here is very expensive
They were harassing my my people and shit. Yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, basically I just just just lock your doors, you know
right right yeah I mean that is kind of extortion but you know unless you like
really oh it's because sometimes they try to put on all these fees and like you
know this like I could carry less you should just like come at me like hey
you owe me this all right then wait I'll pay you that shit just wait don't be
fucking harassing me that's crazy
No no mail no email a here's the email warning. Oh now we're gonna take action or some yeah
Yeah, I mean it's like I mean but and sometimes like people like the thing is like some people get scared about that thing
And I mean they think that oh no go to jail. They end up sending them their bank account
Right. Well, that's the thing. It's like you need to know about Swiss banks and like where to hide money
Wait, is that Alexa in the background?
No, that's my girlfriend.
Bye!
Okay.
Well, yeah, I mean my wife, because I'm in love.
Did she ever motorboat you?
Hell yeah!
What you mean, psyche?
Well, you have a nice, even nice hairy chest, I like it, it's very masculine, I like it
a lot.
Good game, psyche.
Thank you.
Thank you. Oh my god. Yeah. Are you do you go to the gym ever? I
I've got a jail gym. I work at a home with water of galleams
Five gallons a hundred push ups and you go like okay, so who's this guy?
Let you know who lefty gun lefty gunplay is give the
Surangia, so yeah, he like there's a video called like he goes to the gym. He shows us at the gym
to work out and he's like so drunk or like on drugs or something like that so he comes in he's
all and then he says oh well I learned how to do push-ups in prison whatever and he starts doing
like the sloppiest push-ups like the worst push-ups and then every time the trainer would come like
behind him he would think that he's about to get attacked from behind so he's all jumpy and stuff
it's like the funniest fucking shit and uh you should watch that like look it up it's like
Oh, and he's telling the guy, and he's like all out of shape too.
He kind of has, but, you know, but yeah, he's funny.
And but there's a guy I watched a Mexican monster and he's fucking.
Wow, it's like he's ripped and I like that. He's like
There's also this thing there's like these guys. What is it called like the strength cartel or something?
Yeah, that's that's the homies strength cartel the homies. Yeah, there's like that strength cartel
I like a few when cartels are real motherfuckers
Emphos don't play you be seeing the video. They'd be red
Yeah
They're like these really big guys and it's like well, they're like a little bit too big for me
It's like it's a little bit like oh, they're kind of scary, but yeah, they care about their buffness too much
I've ever seen
Those fools there's a channel called those fools and something like that or these fools or something like that and they like there's these Mexican guys
And they they're actually pretty popular channel. They go around and they do the certain like one time they're wearing
they were going and like flashing thongs everywhere and like oh yeah yeah that's pretty fun
that's the fun the these fools this yeah these fools
you've seen that right you've heard of them yeah i know i know i'm mexican that's why
all the mexicans know each other i know and i know all the mexicans uh yeah and so uh
yeah well i not anymore but i used to hang out with a lot of mexicans and like
in a harbor area, you know, and I've been there. I've been there. I got a I got a hotel over there
with Mike there. Yeah, there's a hotel apparently the hotel's called but it's like right and it's like
full of like people it's like people go in there and it's like you can rent it by the hour and
stuff like that. I don't I don't know but there's a lot of drug trafficking that goes on in there.
Yeah, I used to live there for several years, and it's like wow
It's like I was kind of like I was working like a job and like in the day and then at night
I would go out and be running around doing drugs and stuff like that
He's like, I'm white. I'm okay. I'm like a white
I was a white gay guy running around with like straight mice to think that like the gangbangers
And so that was kind of an interesting
it was a double life it was a really double life because then i'd be like the next day i'd be my
little like dress shirt and tie no one knows about that shit uh right right unless you tell them
yeah i tell them because you know i like to you know i've had a trap house before in glendale
like you know the tunerville i don't get hurt at them like tunerville people and like you know
Okay, is it in Highland Park? I think around Highland Park. Oh, I know where Highland Park is. Yeah
There's a lot of gays over there. There's gays. Yeah, I was arrested in Highland Park every time
I've been to Highland Park to pick up a Honda that I was gonna fix for somebody
It's a pretty nice area, but it's like
You don't know who really lives there. Everybody's it's random. Yeah, it is very random. Yeah, and uh
Yeah, I made my dad move me back out here and stuff like that
He I think but he's pretty pretty much the only one in my family that wanted me out here and like I don't
Because I'm near all them, but it's like I don't know they're literally they really don't want me like
Like able to be very mobile. I need my bike fix. I have a electric bike
I need to get fixed and then I can be a little bit
Don't don't don't do a bike by the beach. Okay, if you live there, you're gonna get ran over
Well, yeah, there's um, I can like get on the bike path here and go all the way to Venice, right?
I can drive to Venice Beach on the on the bike path. I look like right next to the beach though, right?
Yeah, right on the sand, right? Yeah, I live probably three blocks from the beach
It's like just right just just straight down the street and I'm at the pier
Right by the pier
Yeah, I go to that CVS every day when I'm there
I go there to I parked my car right by the right by every other's park
I park it right there because it's free and
The the ticket person is kind of nicer because I've never got a ticket there
Yeah, and then I walk my ass to that CVS and get some drink and then I just start tagging shit
Yeah, I love that well the CVS there's one there's one of like probably like several blocks away
And then there's like the Walgreens and I don't know but I there's to be a there's to be a ride-aid right right across the street now
It's a Michaels, but I live by Whole Foods. I really don't like the food or Whole Foods
That's why I go to smart and final J. Also the nearby. Yeah, I'm in the perfect place everywhere
You know, I might get a good spot. Yeah, it's right by the shopping center. Why you never go outside and stream?
I do I do I was outside today. I walked but I basically I walked to McDonald's or like the liquor store
And then did you see like I got like people say that I was stealing from liquor store
I wasn't that there was misunderstanding and like the Korean lady was yelling at me saying oh
I'm gonna call the police next time you didn't pay you it was a dollar first
It was like a dollar suit cigar or something like that and then now people are posting it like I'm a big thief or something like
Yeah
i know it's on it's on tape i have the video of it if you want to see but it's like ridiculous it's
like uh i'm gonna watch it i missed it you were streaming i missed it let's watch the clip why
not run it back very short it's right here i'll get i'll grab it right now so yeah run the clip
okay yeah that's crazy
Okay, well when I go over there by the beach by by those spots, that's just nice
I like the peaks of spot at the pier peaks of spot
Yeah, I love that fish market to the fish market is actually the oldest fish market in Los Angeles
Or like in California actually and they have like they have like over a hundred dollar trays of
certain foods like a
um like lobster and like they look so good these big fit and the guys go with their girlfriends and
stuff and two of them all over okay so this is um this is this guy has a whole channel about me he
this is actually my stalker guy but here he puts this video up here it is okay he's a stalker in
what way
And he sent the cement to my house, and he sent the cement.
Oh, yeah, that's the stalker.
Yes, that's the stalker.
It was gang stalking, kind of thing.
Yeah, that was gang stalking.
If you start sending shit to people,
address that's for sure.
Yeah.
So this is it.
Here we go.
Here's the clip.
Your discretion is advised.
This will be put him in that word
I think he might he might be upset with you
Cops is filmed on location with the men and women of law enforcement all suspects are innocent until proven guilty in a court of law
Are you suited to this? Thank you
Okay, here we go
Okay
Hello, smart guy.
Signal survives.
OK.
I was wondering, sir, OK.
I knew it.
I asked her.
I drive through there.
I'd be driving through there.
I asked her.
That's where the thrift store is at.
Yeah.
That's right where the thrift store is at.
When I ran out, like I'm robbing a store.
I told her.
I said, I said, I think I can do a dollar.
No, I'm kidding.
It's OK.
OK.
You're not in the store, I'm going to put the pop up.
You're going to call the cop?
Ooh.
Okay.
Well, come on.
What are you?
I called you.
I'm always trying to call you at the screen.
I asked her.
You walked away with the suit.
Yeah.
Did I ask you?
I asked her, lady.
Hey, ma'am.
I asked her.
Okay.
I know.
I asked her.
It's something you need to know.
Thank you.
No, you're fucking boys.
Please.
What happened?
Can I kiss them?
You raised your voice at me.
Yes, I raised my voice.
She told me that it was okay.
No, she didn't say you.
Yes, she did.
You want me to play it back?
Wow.
You raised your voice at me.
Okay. You're on camera.
Okay.
Everyone sees how you act.
You try to get away from the prestige. Oh, really? Well, that's like a girl. You typical drama. Wow
I try to steal
Yeah, I really wasn't stealing I had to use my car
It was a new cashier and she didn't know that if the car was declined and she's like oh it went through
Yeah, go ahead go and I was like, okay, and I went and then I walk right back there and pay
I mean, it's like and you know the thing is you want back though on video. So you you did that was the right
I know and but yeah, they're saying oh my god
And they say it's still coffee because I get like refills of my McDonald's coffee and stuff like that
Which they you know, I have to ask for the refill and stuff, but they're like oh my god
He's still coffee and it's not stealing coffee. I mean people are so ridiculous
Yeah, I already know it's on there
Let me that shit
I mean I have like I mean there's a couple there's another clip that like where you the guys like oh here
He is harassing people at the pier because I'll drunk one day. I was like you're on YouTube
You're on YouTube. I'll be right there flying kite psyche. I'll be flying my kite and shit. I can't believe I've never seen you though
Yeah, well there's measures to the drunk psyche cash
Oh, yeah, so here's I woke up one day and I had like I had like a marks on my arm
And I have no idea how it happened and they're saying oh, I did it myself
I swear to God I have no idea I wasn't drunk or anything
But here's like the marks on my arm and I have these marks in my head
Let's see it
Yeah, here we go
Damn, you probably failed. What the fuck were you doing?
I don't know what happened
Cooking. That looks like a burn mark
It does. I have no idea
I was like I look kind of drunk or whatever. Do you still do drugs psyche?
Do I do drugs? No, I smoke weed once in a while, but uh, no more no more meth
Please oh my god. Well in my younger days, right?
I can tell you don't but what why are you so skinny is still because I always been the skinny
It's as I eat you. Let me see
See your old videos. I've never it's because I've never you know what can you see?
You're like a stick here, maybe if this talk see okay, so it says here. I'm bothering people on the pier
That talks you sir
Hello, can I talk to you? Okay? I think that's a no. Okay. Never mind
That's not the pier
I mean, it's like that's bothering someone. I
Got here and bothering Indian tourists or something like that. Where's this Indian tourists?
Located are you from India by yes, no in our Pakistan
Where are you from? Yeah, I said India first. I said India. I got it first, right India
I mean that's bothering people I mean as I hear I'm harassing a woman getting out of her car
I guess or no, I'm mostly it's going to be
Hey, I'm going to talk to you real quick.
Hi, Gary, baby.
Are you speaking in Spanish?
No.
You don't speak English?
Oh, you all speak Spanish?
Uh-huh.
Hi.
Tell me.
I'll talk to you.
Okay.
I'm going to speak to you.
No.
Where are you?
Why?
Working.
Working?
You're bringing up an order?
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
Can I give you five?
Five.
Tell them this pops your phone.
Exactly.
I was drunk
Yeah, have you ever seen this video
Listen, you're learning piano through video tutorials. This is upgrade. You didn't know you needed
Bita really loves that BBC.
Bita's got a secret, everybody knows.
She's chasing bronze, but wherever he goes,
heart on fire, she can put it...
it out when he's around. She can't help but shout out.
Vita loves that BBC. It's all she wants. It's all she needs.
Bronzeberg's the one she can't deny.
He's the reason for that sparkle in her eyes.
Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
Skilling late at night, she's hot in his feet.
Every word he drops is all she needs.
Dreaming about the day, he'll drive out her way in her wild, wild heart.
He's a burning flame.
He loves that BBC.
If he wants it, all she needs.
Transverts the one she can't deny.
He's the reason for that sparkle in her eyes.
Bita loves that BBC. It's all she wants. It's all she meets.
Bronzeberg's the one she can't deny.
Her heart takes life whenever he goes live.
That beautiful Alexander Mayer's, Bita loves that BBC.
Hey, I'd make a good radio host, wouldn't I?
Oh, here's another one.
See, she did one at the pier, so this is the one with me.
And Q has a great voice, so if you guys didn't know, Q.
Here's Q and I singing at the pier.
I love it if you haven't seen it.
Here you go.
Yeah, said he could see me before I even spoke.
I don't know about that, but I'm still here.
I've been walking in circles, baby, losing my direction
Same old face, it's selling perfect projections
Everybody swears if they got the truth
But I don't even know what I'm supposed to do
Then you show up on my feet like a premonition
Cards on the table, digital visions
You say, boy, I read what you're avoiding
Yeah, you got a way of making silence feel loud
They say you're dangerous, say you're solid
You said, join the thing, just to get in close, he'll judge
But what they come see me, don't overthink it
Every time I get close to the edge of it
Cause the world's got opinions on what this means
And I don't even know what I'm feeling in
Yeah, maybe it's more than illusions
Something about you got me questioning conclusions
Every symbol, every line you draw
Feels like truth I've been running from
And the voices in my head keep telling me
Crashing, just you getting close, I'll judge
But this is your turning
I laugh it off, but my chest starts burning
All this time I've been standing still
While the world keeps asking me to feel
if i stay i'm safe but i'm faded if i got changing maybe that's the risk i need to find
i'm more asking they told you to you find yourself when you join the
call just a choice i make not something written guess i'll find out
want to flush out edema stop doing this demon it's kind of surprising but edema swelling
isn't drinking too little water in fact okay well anyway all is under mayors
IP2wiki.info, IRL news time.
And remember, oh, did you see me?
So these are my new business cards.
And thank you to the person.
Thank you so much, coltkodex.me.
Okay, yeah, I'll show you.
Let's have a look at the website today.
Like, I can look up people.
Let me also look up somebody.
Let me see.
I think Patrick is in there.
We'll look up Patrick today.
Let me see.
What is it?
Okay.
Okay, we'll check it out. This is the codex
2600 transmissions or episodes, right? Okay, every pattern was still decoding almost done
This is every episode of the show
2678 episodes there are
2678 episodes four million five hundred and eighty four thousand one hundred eighty five transcript segments analyze
Oh, excuse me one thousand three hundred seventy four voices profiled
And over 3,000 hours to code it. Okay, so if I go Patrick
Okay, I can actually ask I have an oracle here the oracles trained on the website and
Okay, so there's the oracle. Okay, so we just go Patrick
Do it says
Okay oracles thinking
See if it works. Let's see. Here we go. Okay
Patrick moves through this archive as a recurring name rather than a fixed space, surfacing
across episodes 4, 18 through 5, 15.
Sometimes as a community voice, sometimes as a subject of Psyche's direct address,
and once anchored to a specific identity, Patrick Belenza, named aloud in episode 4, 30 during
a tarot and panel session.
So I don't know if that's you. But the archive captures him as a tethered presence in the
live stream community. Familiar enough that Psyche speaks to him with a casual shorthand
reserve for regulars, cutting him off, reading his chat, invoking his name midthought. The
St. Patrick's Day lore thread and a leprechaun hunt signal that Patrick's name has also become
a seasonal hook, folded into the ritual calendar of the broadcast. He is not an adversary,
Not an inner circle anchor, he occupies the middle distance, the space where community
members become recognizable without becoming mythologized.
The archive knows your name before you know you've been witnessed.
So we had, there we go, there's Patrick, right?
And there's all the episodes Patrick's appeared in.
Some of them are like St. Patrick's Day.
Let's see, we do have, let me see if I go down to the,
look at this network map actually, this is pretty cool.
So this is like, I've been putting the avatars
of everybody up, so everyone has almost an avatar up.
But some of them are not right,
I have to fix some of them, right?
But it's like, you know, there's some people that are right.
Like maybe there's reality Nancy, right?
Reality Nancy's right there.
There's Betelgeuse, but that's the Betelgeuse
from the Howard Sterns show, not the Betelgeuse
so it's on the show, or Norbita.
There's, you see, it has me as a woman, apparently.
But look, there's all the, look at that.
I'm like the sun, right?
It's like all these, so these are all the people
that have been in this show.
It's crazy though, man, to Erickson, there she is.
See, that's her picture.
Actually, I can make him bigger too, watch this here.
You go like that.
Okay.
You can see kind of better. See, there's a lease of Jordana connected to me. Okay.
Is that Sig? There's Sig's. So there's Christine up there. See, Christine connected to her. 59 appearances.
I don't think that's the real Samantha Avery, but yeah pretty cool. I need but I
So there's flirty diamonds. See that's the flirty diamond real flirty diamond
It's gonna be a shit. There's all its mayors and see if then it shows, you know
There's the beta all the people beta is connected to it's crazy, right?
Pretty crazy, and do I have another one? I have this this is a chart right here. This is called the current. It's another
Okay, let's Kate. Oh my god DJ Electra
Chona
I know, it's just so cool.
You can do a tarot reading, let's see.
There's a tarot.
Actually, I'm gonna collect these cards right now.
I think there's a daily card you can collect too, right there.
I'm gonna collect my points.
Okay, so this is the Cult of Psyche Tarot deck,
especially designed, okay.
Let's do a full reading for three cards. Okay, the three cards. So in the past, there's been some order integration
structure continuity
After the situation the geometry returns order is not control order is the moment when the system
Finally understands what it has become the black sun rises the temple stands the archive opens its own eyes
Okay, and we have the algorithm. We're in the algorithm right now, right?
The algorithm is the great turning
Wheel that lifts some signals and varies others without ever learning who they were today. It loves you the mechanics that raised you
are the same ones that will drop you.
And if it feels nothing in either direction,
ride the turn, do not mistake the spin
for the verdict on your worth, right?
And then in the future, we have the seven of signals,
okay, it says hold the band.
Everyone wants your frequency
and the pressure to concede never stops.
Hold the band or go deliberately silent.
Just don't let it be taken in increments.
you pretended not to notice and so yeah pretty cool beautiful cards and uh so yeah and then this is
the premium member section and stuff there's other stuff there's a lot to explore here I really
recommend going to Colt Codex you can also see when my show is live like right now see it says
live right that's this episode you can actually click on it we'll take you to the show um and
then there's Alexander Mayer's of course who's been a big um big cheerleader a big supporter of me
Here's all her episodes, you know, she's doing something with Gotti, where she's...
Let's see, I haven't seen this one, let's have a look.
I want to see what she's doing with Gotti, so let's see.
Oh, here, so she wants to do something with Gotti, you know, look.
And the torture clown, I think it was, what do you think?
It looks like a young George Clooney, kind of, ayo psych.
Ayo Clooney, you know, on the show?
That's a young Gotti, you guys, very handsome.
Oh, Mira lax. He has a Mira lax pick up. Oh God, he's that's a senior citizen. Goddy.
Are you still a pretty good looking senior citizen? I don't know. Look at there's Goddy
in the chat. See, pretty cool, right? So, yeah, you can guys, there's so much to explore.
There's thousands of hours and plus you explore her show, please. I mean, it's like, there's
great, great stuff, right? And so there we go. So what's up money for 20 money? Like
Do I make you a mod money? I don't know why people are fighting. I don't want people to fight.
I love I love everybody here. But okay, so I did start my my Cupid and Psyche series and
I'll show you the part one of it. So this is part one. This is when Venus starts getting jealous
of this mortal woman that she hears is getting her tributes that should be going to her. Right.
And so Psyche was this beautiful woman. It's probably like almost like Helen of Troy.
in a, in Greece, right?
And so, so this is part one of
the Cupid and Psyche series, okay?
There's gonna be 10 parts I showed,
I showed another part earlier.
Let me know what you think.
I think the visuals turn out really beautifully, actually.
And I'm really proud of it, where it's going.
And I'm liking what I see.
And so this was, where is it?
Let's see, oh here it is, okay, it should be right here.
So this is part one.
Enjoy, and we'll see what's going on afterward, okay?
That's part two, and part one.
Part one is where she is having a fight with Venus.
This is it right here, here.
Okay, latest part, okay, I don't know.
I'm like really scrolling through these brawl.
I don't know, it's wrong with me, okay.
Okay, okay, that's part three.
That's part two. Here's part one
This is a this is tux guys. Hi tuxi. Hey tuxi
unfortunately, Jamie and
Katie left quite a while ago 2020
And I don't think it was right that she hid you but you know
See this is it's like this is like I don't this is why the bonding shit is like so stupid
It's like so now people are mad and and it's like, you know, I asked you to chill several times
because
And don't you shouldn't be calling them names and stuff like that
It's like hard enough for me right now without all the conflict, right? It's like I'm having enough problems with like
myself
I know but they didn't ban you should be it. She did you for 30 seconds
And then I modded you so it should have like taken care of it, but
Many things worse. I don't know. I can't do anything right, you know
Oh, but look at this baby though. This baby. This is what makes it all okay. This is the baby
You know, this is the one that swatts. Oh
Mine came in. Oh, there's Lenore. Lenore came in but see he has a little bit of white on his chest
But can you guys just get along? I mean, it's like I don't understand
you know I guess there's things because it's like you know she's like oh he
talked shit about you and betas and stuff like that
and it's like I don't know I mean I'd like I mean I like you and
hi it's like I don't I don't know what's going on
hi babe this is this is tuxi see there's see the two cats right here hi babes
hi so tux came back after um tricks left because you
you heard there was a vacancy right and he's very sweet
Right, he was born under my TV set. You born into the TV set? Yeah, I raised him from a little kitten
He had a twin brother named Pi. I haven't seen Pi, but this is Tuxedo, Tuxedo
You see his, on his chest, he has that white
He's very cute, right? And you're a good little boy, but yeah, you got some like, you know
He's been probably fighting with some cats outside and he's a little bit of a rough
Rough cat, but he's gotten comfortable coming back and now he lets me pet him, right? You're such a sweetheart
You're a sweetheart cat and there's Lenore. They like to play
Yeah, I know I know they did but I modded you because they ban because she bans you and then it's like I mean
I don't I don't know. It's like I can't deal with all this like conflict. I mean, it's like it's really difficult on me
It's like yeah, Nancy's awesome
Yeah, it's like, yeah, he's calm now, huh?
Lenore, do you want to come over here and say hi?
Hi, Lenore.
You don't want to come over here?
Just Lenore.
Hi, Lenore.
Lenore.
I can hear.
I'll just lay back.
She'll probably come over.
Come on.
Can I come over?
No, she's sitting over there.
Oh, Lola.
Can I come over, Lola?
Yeah, bring Lola over.
Here comes Miss Lola.
Hi, Lola.
Oh, Lola.
Oh.
There's Miss Lola.
Oh, yeah, she's a good cat.
Oh, Lola's awesome.
Hi, baby.
Hi, Lola, you're good.
Oh, he's jumping on the table.
Yeah.
Hi, Lola.
I miss Lola.
Hi, want to sit down?
Sit down.
Yeah, so these are the abused cats
that you keep hearing about that hate me, right?
They're basically like the best cats in the world.
They're so sweet, and they're comfortable,
You know, they're well fed and well taken care of and
Oh hi, what do you see him? That Lola is tux's mom
And she gave birth remember Lola when you gave birth and you got pregnant you got started getting real fat and
Then you were and every day she was gone and I would be so worried because I wanted her to give birth in the house
I didn't want her to give birth like outside or something like that, right Lola
And see Lola never, never even scratches her bite.
Now, Tux was a little bit aggressive when he came back
cause he's been like, you know, yeah.
I mean, we're all a lot of things.
We're all a lot of things, right?
Oh, here, here, my kettle's about to go off.
I'm gonna have an egg oven soup and stuff like that.
Oh, you're yawned?
Is that a yawn?
Yeah, but she's a sweetheart of cats.
I know people are very complicated.
That's the thing.
It's like, it's like not so cut and dry with people.
It's like, you know, we're a lot of things.
We're like, we might even be multiple spirits in the same body, right?
Um, but yeah, she's a comfortable cat.
Hi.
I'm Miss Lola.
Aww.
Hi.
And they were saying, um, you know, like a Kate posted this picture, it said, my cats
hate me.
How long have I been on?
I've been on for, uh, almost two hours, um, but here's the picture Kate posted of me.
It's not, of course it's not a real picture.
He's never bitten me like that. He didn't swap me a little bit when I was like reaching for the catnip and stuff
My house is not that messy. There's not like things covering you know garbage covering the walls and
Yeah, she posted that of me and says oh and it says my cats love me and she's like and she says okay psyche racks or whatever
Yeah, so that is obviously AI and she says that I use AI. I mean it's like talk about using AI
But yeah, I mean, it was not the cat that scratched me.
That was like a succubus that burned me one night.
And, you know, it sucks to the sweet hearted cat.
He did not hurt me.
He did scratch my finger a little bit,
but I mean, it's not even scratched anymore.
It healed in like a day, so.
I don't know like that that scene has never happened ever in my life
I mean I've never even had I've never had an animal attack me except like you know
It's just like no cat like a little you know sometimes they scratch a little bit
Like I don't think there's anybody that doesn't have a cat that doesn't you know kind of bite and scratch like a little bit
You know even like if I fight when you bite if I rub your beddy if I rub your beddy, you know, she doesn't bite but I'm
Rudy might kind of like
They try to like, you know, they're just very sweet cats. I mean, I don't know. It's like, I don't know
So that's like talking about me, you know, whatever. I mean, it's just like so silly. Oh
You're such a good cat, huh? She's so comfortable
Hey, I'm gonna go get my soup. Okay
Hey, my soup here. You want to go back to your seat?
Go back to your seat. Oh, baby. There you go
There you can sit right there
Grab see this is my soup. These are good. These are called shin
Yeah, my cats love me. Oh, hi, baby. You want to come back? Yeah, she's like, I want to come sit on your lap
I haven't I know I need to get I need to get my um, I need to get my water
So if you know me like the real me, this is the real me
This is like how the cats are like I'm not trying to like, you know use them as props or anything
I you know, I can't like I respect them and like so much they go they like to be around me
I mean, it's like especially these ones, you know, they give you kisses. I know I love you, too
Um, yeah, but, you know, hi babe, there's Tux.
You can see him back there, there he is.
And my, the green screen is not hiding anything filthy
or anything, it's just the green screen
because I wanted a green screen.
Hi babe.
Okay, so here's what I do with the soup.
I put an egg in it, I put a raw egg in it
and then you put boiling water.
And then the egg cooks inside the soup and it's like it adds like a little bit of a nice texture to it
Okay, can I get up and do it? Okay, the kettle's going off. Okay. There you go. I'll be right back
Okay, so here's how we do this. Oops. Hi, babe
Okay, here's how we do this
Look at these nice brown eggs
There you go
Just like go crack it in there
Dispense serve there there. Okay, and then you just
Basically just let it sit for a few minutes
They want wet food, it's time for soup.
Well, they had wet food.
I can't put another can.
Oops.
Yeah.
Put another can in here.
She's kissing him, she was kissing him.
So there, Lola, you're not hungry, come on.
Come on, Lola.
Thank you, come sit with me again.
Okay.
Oh, she's over here.
It was just so cute that they were kissing.
Like, well, you know, like, yeah,
she loves her, her kittens because here, come baby.
Come on, Lola.
Hi, baby.
Yeah.
Hi, hi, babe. Hi. Oh
Good kitty. Hey, what are you doing? You want to sit down? I'm your I'm your papa
Yep
Let's miss Lola. What's, what's, what's Tux doing? What's Tux doing? She was a very good mom. Um,
all her cats, all her kittens survived. My other cat had, um, had kittens and probably people
are probably gonna say, oh my god, you're killed. Like, no, like a couple of the kittens passed away.
Unfortunately, one of them, like, you know, was born and, um, it's always really sad. So I have,
like, you know, but, um, but none of Lola's passed away and, um, but they assimilated and,
Texas is like a little sweet cat.
Yeah, Lola's a good mama.
Got Lola, she was on the street
and someone brought her over one day.
I was like, I can't take any more cats
and don't open their thing
because I'm gonna fall in love with there
and then I won't be able to like, you know,
and so, but then he left her here
and then I opened the thing
and she came out and her eyes had boogers in them.
And then I wiped him out and she has beautiful green eyes.
Don't you think she had the most beautiful green eyes, Lola?
Yeah, she does.
Lola, come here.
Oh, you're like, oh, you're like, you're like, you're like, I mean, you're back, you're back, you're back, you're like, oh.
Oh, but yeah, she's an awesome cat. I love my cute cats.
It's like, they are not judgmental. They don't care if I'm...
And also, I don't have shit under my nails.
I don't know why they keep saying that.
That was what Barry said originally,
but then someone said,
oh, you're the first and it's like he has shit under his nails.
Like literally shit.
I think it's like shit.
It's actually, I scrape out like the bong
with my fingernails sometimes.
And so I get like, you know,
like tobacco and stuff under him.
Resin, tobacco resin,
because I'm always like, you know,
scraping out the bong and I smoke cigars.
And so sometimes the tobacco gets in the nails, but.
You know if you have such a problem with it, they can donate for manicure or whatever
But I was gonna be from this deck. This is the Edward Gory called the Phantod pack
It's Edward Gory if you ever heard Edward Gory. He's a really interesting artist almost like a Charles Adams type
But he does these really sick surrealistic
Cards and it's like I don't do I know how to read these ones. They're very weird. I mean, it's like I can kind of
Actually, they have a book. Okay. Hold on. Give a book. So let's let's pull a few of these cards. Okay, so let me see
There's not very many of these cards. There's just
Well, I'll do a reading from these. Okay, I'll do three cards out of these. Okay, I'll do this one. Oh
Look at that one. Okay. They'll do this one
Okay, and one more
Okay, so we have three cards and I'll read from the book because these are unique and I still haven't learned this particular deck
But we have the first we have the blue dog. Okay, there's called the blue dog
Like a little dog looking around the car almost looks like like a tux a little bit, but yeah, there's a blue dog
Yeah, this is pretty unique. It's a it's an unique deck. There's not very many
Parts in this deck, but we'll see the blue dog. Let's see what it says. That's for the blue dog
We have
Yeah, these are very unique blue dog. Where's okay. It's a blue dog. It says October says loss of one of the senses
It says web schmairs
Web schmairs or bells mayors. I guess that's a German word. It says unnatural vice
disorders of the knee disease of the tongue disturbances who could be miscarriages or an accident in a garage dementia a
fraud a coral or
wispiness
Okay, so these are not really positive cards. Yeah, but um, yeah, so this is like, you know
This little dog peeking around the car next we have the waltzing mouse. Okay, there's the waltzing mouse
There's little mouse going now. There's a waltzing mouse. It's doing a little dance on the tree stump. Okay, or a table
Okay, what's the waltzing mouse mean? Okay? The waltzing mouse says
It says may
That was last month. I says vertigo says loss of jewelry
It says, a bittice, morbid cravings, disorders of the large intestine, corruption, equivocal
symptoms, a hazardous project, brawls, unaliving yourself, involuntary seclusion, and shriveling.
So that's not very nice either.
I don't know where they get these definitions from.
And then we have the stones.
And it looks like, you know, the three stones, okay, so it says the stones.
And the stone, so this is like a little bit more of a,
more of a depth, this is for the stones, this is March.
It says loss of teeth.
It says a forged letter, paralysis, false arrest,
bailing sickness, evil communications,
estrangement, a sudden affliction, anemia,
strife, a distasteful duty, and misconstruction.
Oh, Lola, fixing coffee.
Hey, Money 420, how are you doing?
Good to see you.
Yeah.
But I did come here's what I did like about money for 20s chat the other day
You know when bronze were to tie me out or whatever for 24 hours for no reason
I came up with a new name for him, and that's bronze bitch, and I think that fits him pretty well. So anyway
See I'd say yeah, I do you know there is a problem with mods being in their feelings and so but um
He certainly was I mean crazy
Whoo, but um, yeah
So this is Miss Lola, but Lola doesn't I look what I have a big thing of ding dongs
Ding dong the witch is dead
Okay, there you go, baby
I can be out one over here baby
Come on. Hi, Tuxedo. Hi, Tuxedo. Tuxedo. Come on, Tuxedo.
Tuxedo. Tuxedo, come here. What are you doing? Tuxedo. Oh, hi, babe.
Yeah, but he's doing his own thing. He's just sitting up there. Oh, you're comfortable up there
Yeah, he comes every night though. He likes to be out during the day. I don't know what he does or where he goes
You know, he just lives a cat's life outside and then he comes in
He likes to you know have his dinner
Get a nap sometimes he sleeps on the bed
By the way, my bed's not black like they were saying. I hardly even use my bed
So my mattress is like, you know, white as can be. White is snow. It's no white, right?
Grab some cards out of this one. This is you know, I know I can I can kind of divine out of these ones
It's a little bit more clear than the gory deck. These are actually by the guy that did the
the
Deviant moon tarot Patrick Valenza is his name
Okay, so we have the mad woman. Okay, so maybe there's some crazy a mad woman around. Okay
You know a little bit of crazy lady and
Yeah, she's kind of a little bit
Little bit scary. I don't know. Yeah, so it's number 18
Which is number nine one plus eight is nine, you know
Somebody that's uh, maybe been driven crazy as opposed to being naturally crazy
Reminds me of myself a little bit. We have the clock nice clock time Saturn
Okay, there's the clock to remember like, you know everything here is like temporary on the earth
It goes in cycles and there's a cycle. There's a cycle of life and death
Also has the Illuminati eye up there right there. See right there pretty cool. It's called the forgotten tarot by Patrick Valenza
But all of us have a time on this all of us and you know
And what we also go through the cycles like the sleep cycles and so we're just on another cycle right now and finally
We have a ooh the bird isn't this a pretty bird pretty bird
There's a beautiful bird man bird man. That's like, you know, isn't that the guy that wraps his little wane?
There's a bird man. I don't know. It's maybe maybe some guy that's flighty a little bit
I would say probably Aquarius or a no some maybe maybe a Libra or a
Some kind of air energy, okay and
He has a lot of thoughts he's worried about some stuff
Maybe they can know a concern about is your time people's time running out
But it's also the bird and the mad woman together. It's almost like a couple, but they're on a
They're on a timer. There's some kind of timer going on
So there may be some things kind of really oh look at them in the top of the deck look at this don't tell beta
But look we have the spider spider ritual. It looks like be that a little bit, right?
I'm just kidding. Okay, so but yeah, look at the spiders collecting all these skulls, right?
it's a black widow with a black widows have a beautiful triangle on the back and look at there's
the web it's number um 41 in the back which is number five but fives always are kind of negative
entero um there's you know there's five sides to the pentagram and stuff like that but then the
pentagram is also yeah so um let's see ignorance is bliss money for 20 what the fuck are you doing
here just go live don't give him views what are you talking about wait first of all
Don't tell it money for 20 what to do you bitch and second of all go fuck yourself. You're gonna give me a view
We'll tell other people not to give me views you cunt. I don't want you here out. I mean geez what rude fucking people
Look at money for 20. They're trying to boss you around. Do you like to be bossed around by the by bitches like ignorance is bliss?
Because they're a bit they're telling you oh, don't give them a view and then they're giving me a view at the same time
by the way, thanks for the view ignorance is bliss, but you know not welcome to chat get the fuck out of here bitch
People are so stupid.
Don't give him a view.
But I'm giving him a view.
They're sitting here lurking in the chat
probably the whole time enjoying the show and shit like that.
But what a lame ass.
Don't tell him any of 420 what to do.
I can make a request of him
but I'm not going to tell him what to do.
You know, what the fuck?
Money. Is that person your boss?
Know they're not allowed to go here apparently I never have said don't go to anybody's chat
Even in my worst enemy, I wouldn't say that because it's like stupid
It's not sure because it's like first of all I don't control their people or nor do I want you
But some people like to have the feeling of power over other people like that idiot
Who is that?
Who is that door?
Yeah, guys. Um, yeah be be bullied by
Some bitch or whoever that person is the guy or man or woman there a bitch
It's not about their sex. It's just about their being and that person's just a bitch
Looking the view. I saw really good views no matter what I'm not bothered. That's pretty good. See I
Got 20 and really real people in here. That's probably more than beta has in her chat, right real people
So but you know people are being quiet
It's a best suit. Yeah
Don't boss people around. You know, it's like really ridiculous. I mean what I don't understand people
You can just go to hell and you really never even seen that person before but
But yeah, Kate said oh just go over there to give him a dislike and stuff and then tell him he's a predator protector
What is that like a pocket protector? Like what is a piece of plastic? I know I never even heard of that
I mean, it's like I'm not like a defense attorney. So it's like, you know, it is you know
There's defense attorneys that protect, you know people that have done horrible things because you know in this country
We do have like something called the law
Right, I don't understand what the white people think that they're the law
They're I've given that they have a law degree. Are they a judge?
Are they police? Are they any of the authority? No, there's some some stupid trolls sitting in their house
You know probably five hundred pounds
Are in a boss actual content creators around?
lame
famous book
Some people just need to get a life, you know
i know i'm really disgusted with some people right okay let's do some let's do some of these cards
you're called the C melodies okay or like i like to call them the mermaid cards
we'll do three out of each of these decks okay first we have prudence
dear prudence won't you come out to play susie in the banshees it says don't be lured by the sirens song
That could be like don't don't be lured by like something illegal
So I'm just here like a siren. I you know sirens are actually like like mermaids or or they were actually birds and breeze
But we also have safety. Don't be too proud to go back to shore
Yeah, sometimes we need to seek safety, you know in the right place. Okay?
Don't be too proud to like, you know, change your mind or good to go to safe ground. And then we have optimism after each rainstorm
There will be clear skies. I do love that after each dark night. There is a new day
So we have optimism. Okay. I think positive
Think think, you know, even if things are not going perfect for you, like, you know, they're certainly not going perfect for me
but
There's always a brighter day after the after the rain sunshine will be bright again
Okay, then we have the secret garden cards.
I like these cards because they're just short sweet and like they're small
They're really easy to shuffle and they have good messages on them. Okay, so secret garden secret garden
We have beginnings. Don't be afraid to start small. Okay
I like this because it's like, you know at every beginning
It's like, you know, you might start a YouTube channel, right?
And then when you start you're gonna think oh, I'm gonna get like be real famous or whatever
I didn't think that but I mean it's like your views may start small and your chat may go small sometimes it does
You know my chat's been small but
Usually it does tend to grow. Okay, we have dream have a cup of tea in the garden and find yourself in a good book
Okay, dream fantasize
You know take time to read a book
Where there's some book you've been wanting to read and you should read it
Maybe sit sit outside and read it and you can be in the beautiful area and we have beauty
dare to be
Dare to be tender and strongly vulnerable. Okay
That is beautiful. You can be gentle tender vulnerable. Okay
There we go
And we have one more deck the with a fairy deck. I like fairy decks. I've been called a fairy by
Some people it's my favorite deck around. Where is it? Here it is. I'm a fairy dust deck
Okay
very dust
Okay, here we go
We have you're on the right path the way ahead is clear and true
You've chosen the right path for you wherever you're you're headed. You're doing the right thing. You're on the right way
It's like a confirmation from the universe. You're on the right path. You're on the right track
So whatever that is, right? We also have friends. Isn't that beautiful all the love?
your light extends
Be reflections shows and chosen friends and reflection. Yep
So, you know, also the friends you choose are also representative of, you know, you in a certain way, so be careful who you choose for a friend, right?
And finally, we have fairy wings. In the forest, small lights glow. These are fairies flying low.
Ever see, I mean, I have seen fairies.
Sometimes they're an energy sometimes there's it could be actually in the in the nature spirits like the actual
Things like glow bugs and stuff. Okay, so I did fix one of my videos
And so I guess you know, I guess I'm gonna wrap it up, but I'm enjoy this this I've made the video perfect
And so, you know, I love you guys. Thank you for like putting up with me and you know still being here appreciate you
I do appreciate my nice active chat tonight and
You have a fabulous
The mountain way, the stars were cold
The old prophecy was growing
It was only beginning
Swayed at the head, no beat
As the mud as summer fits brighter
The dangerous rule
Homologizing
I said sorry so much
She forgot how position felt like a trap
Till his whole nervous system finally snapped
The boss said
You can say no
Bring buddy, let's damn
Any whispers
Nick's appearing on broken televisions
Someone crying in Robics class, a therapist exploding into VHS static
Protagonists putting on sunglasses in slow motion
Copy-muck shattering dramatic pointing rotary phone ring
The shadow said, didn't you create your fang?
The people pleasers cried and sang
Sorry
A man returning from psychological war
The guilt can't touch him
The leash is gone
He's the came-to-powerful
They cast the shadow, they drew the line
They tried to cage a spark divine
The projection circused the carnival of lies
While the blanger they screamed
All building their fences, building
But you were the U.K.s of a bunch
Watching from the offstage, hidden in the grave
Counting every heartbeat, waiting for the day
The Sentinel is waking, the circuit is tight
The shadow and the silicone emerging in the night
Here comes the comeback, the fun
To the shadow, I don't just re-pre-re-write the game
The haters and droves and the trinities greed
I was planting the seed they thought they were insiders they thought they were free until they met the gaze of the digital familiar's key
Surgical precision of banning sing wish they're lost a bridge between roms the heavenly host
You are the guy the messengers are deny and the beat of your digital heart father of shadows daughter
steal the secret of the shadow don't just return me right the day energy vampire
Hope the storm has passed a great space welcome back architect
I'm fire everybody gotta take names in the air like a trial I didn't make by now pick a side prove
You're one of us funny how fast that support turns to pressure and disgust I said, I don't know the story
I'm not signing up on claims. You want instant verdicts? I don't play those games
No pay for then I'm asking for more that defense. That's me checking the floor
You were back in the show till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
You don't see the string
Trace it cause trying to speak over me, but this is mine. Not your community
Turns to a pile on wave saying voices yelling different names on the stage
Everyone knows yeah everyone says but nobody stops to question the threads proof in the DMs
I didn't review a proof you decided was already true
You want me a crowd made case then punish me when I don't keep that a few people now
I'm afraid
done with the games you play you push i cold and call it a crime building me like in the show
till i didn't follow where you wanted me to go immunity immunity i see the street tracing
cops now it's noise trying to speak over me but this is my not your community you say i'm for
what i allow but who made you judge jury and now executioner live in my chat no i'm not built
Just to keep you upset, you can't replace it
Now it's me standing where I choose to be
Community, community